[Music]
want to know about the exciting services
available
on the icici bank imobile payer
let's take you through them one by one
login to imobile pay app click discover
on the dashboard here you will find a
host of services that you can avail
with just a few clicks for example
spending overview provides an overview
of inflow and outflow
of money spent month wise transaction
timeline helps you view the amount
debited
and credited from your savings account
and credit card
in upcoming transactions you can view
your future upcoming transactions
based on your current payment pattern
my pre-approved offers helps you check
all your pre-approved offers
provided to you by icici bank like
pre-approved home loan
personal loan car loan credit card and
more
in service requests you can view the
status of your raised service requests
like new debit card delivery status
applied loan status and more
the tips for you service provides you
tips on how to protect your card
bill payments advice spends overview and
more
isn't it exciting that you can access
and avail so many services instantly
from the comfort of your home that's not
all
click on services on the dashboard and
you will discover
a long list of great services that you
can benefit from
for example click on account services
following other services manage standing
instructions
helps you manage all your si
with add or manage pays you can add a
pay
in your account transfer funds
in add or manage billers you can add a
biller
to your account and pay all your bills
directly from your account
in link accounts you can link your other
accounts like
loan credit card and dmat account
etc with your savings account
with transfer your accounts you can
transfer your bank account
from one branch to another easily
with form 15g or 15h
you can get your form 15 g or h easily
in view tds certificate you can view and
download your tds certificate
view interest certificate you can view
and download your interest certificate
the list goes on your mmid
it is a mobile money identifier service
you can view your mm id allotted for
your account number
in view rewards points you can easily
check your reward points in pmjjby
you can enroll for pradhan mantri bhima
yojana
in request to redispatch deliverables
you can request for redispatch of your
undelivered banking items
like cards checkbook etc
in request for family banking you can
open your family bank account
at icici bank in update
employer name you can update your
employer name in case of salary account
similarly if you click on insta banking
services
on the services dashboard you will
discover an equally exciting list of
great services like
transaction history view history of your
transactions
cash deposit you can deposit cash into
your account
through imobile pay which means you
don't need to fill a bank slip at the
branch to deposit cash
with cash withdrawal you can withdraw
cash from your savings account
without filling cash withdrawal slips
with fund transfer you can transfer
funds to other accounts
with request dd or po raise request for
demand draft or po
with just a few clicks
in checklist withdrawal you can withdraw
money from your savings account
without using a self withdrawal check
with update email id or email statement
registration
you can update your email id so that you
can get your bank statement mailed
directly to your registered email id
update pan you can update your pan
through your mobile
without visiting the bank with a
physical copy
discover one great service after another
on your imobile pay app
login to the icici bank imobile pay app
and experience the ease of banking